{
    "qa_turn1": {
        "FAC": "find all facility entities  in the context.",
        "GPE": "find all geo political entities  in the context.",
        "LOC": "find all location entities  in the context.",
        "ORG": "find all organization entities  in the context.",
        "PER": "find all person entities  in the context.",
        "VEH": "find all vehicle entities  in the context.",
        "WEA": "find all weapon entities  in the context."
    },
    "qa_turn2": {
        "('FAC', 'ART', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'ART', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'ART', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'ART', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'ART', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'ART', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'ART', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'GEN-AFF', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'GEN-AFF', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'GEN-AFF', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'GEN-AFF', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'GEN-AFF', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'GEN-AFF', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'GEN-AFF', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'ORG-AFF', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'ORG-AFF', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'ORG-AFF', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'ORG-AFF', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'ORG-AFF', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'ORG-AFF', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'ORG-AFF', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'PART-WHOLE', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'PART-WHOLE', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'PART-WHOLE', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'PART-WHOLE', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'PART-WHOLE', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'PART-WHOLE', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'PART-WHOLE', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'PER-SOC', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a person social relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'PER-SOC', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a person social relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'PER-SOC', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a person social relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'PER-SOC', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a person social relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'PER-SOC', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a person social relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'PER-SOC', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a person social relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'PER-SOC', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a person social relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'PHYS', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a physical relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'PHYS', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a physical relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'PHYS', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a physical relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'PHYS', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a physical relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'PHYS', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a physical relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'PHYS', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a physical relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('FAC', 'PHYS', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a physical relationship with facility entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'ART', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'ART', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'ART', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'ART', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'ART', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'ART', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'ART', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'GEN-AFF', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'GEN-AFF', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'GEN-AFF', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'GEN-AFF', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'GEN-AFF', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'GEN-AFF', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'GEN-AFF', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'ORG-AFF', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'ORG-AFF', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'ORG-AFF', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'ORG-AFF', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'ORG-AFF', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'ORG-AFF', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'ORG-AFF', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'PART-WHOLE', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'PART-WHOLE', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'PART-WHOLE', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'PART-WHOLE', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'PART-WHOLE', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'PART-WHOLE', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'PART-WHOLE', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'PER-SOC', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a person social relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'PER-SOC', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a person social relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'PER-SOC', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a person social relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'PER-SOC', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a person social relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'PER-SOC', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a person social relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'PER-SOC', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a person social relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'PER-SOC', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a person social relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'PHYS', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a physical relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'PHYS', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a physical relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'PHYS', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a physical relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'PHYS', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a physical relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'PHYS', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a physical relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'PHYS', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a physical relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('GPE', 'PHYS', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a physical relationship with geo political entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'ART', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'ART', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'ART', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'ART', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'ART', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'ART', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'ART', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'GEN-AFF', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'GEN-AFF', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'GEN-AFF', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'GEN-AFF', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'GEN-AFF', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'GEN-AFF', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'GEN-AFF', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'ORG-AFF', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'ORG-AFF', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'ORG-AFF', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'ORG-AFF', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'ORG-AFF', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'ORG-AFF', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'ORG-AFF', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'PART-WHOLE', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'PART-WHOLE', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'PART-WHOLE', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'PART-WHOLE', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'PART-WHOLE', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'PART-WHOLE', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'PART-WHOLE', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'PER-SOC', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a person social relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'PER-SOC', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a person social relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'PER-SOC', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a person social relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'PER-SOC', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a person social relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'PER-SOC', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a person social relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'PER-SOC', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a person social relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'PER-SOC', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a person social relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'PHYS', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a physical relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'PHYS', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a physical relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'PHYS', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a physical relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'PHYS', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a physical relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'PHYS', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a physical relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'PHYS', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a physical relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('LOC', 'PHYS', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a physical relationship with location entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'ART', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'ART', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'ART', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'ART', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'ART', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'ART', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'ART', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'GEN-AFF', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'GEN-AFF', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'GEN-AFF', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'GEN-AFF', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'GEN-AFF', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'GEN-AFF', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'GEN-AFF', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'ORG-AFF', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'ORG-AFF', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'ORG-AFF', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'ORG-AFF', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'ORG-AFF', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'ORG-AFF', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'ORG-AFF', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'PART-WHOLE', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'PART-WHOLE', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'PART-WHOLE', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'PART-WHOLE', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'PART-WHOLE', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'PART-WHOLE', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'PART-WHOLE', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'PER-SOC', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a person social relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'PER-SOC', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a person social relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'PER-SOC', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a person social relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'PER-SOC', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a person social relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'PER-SOC', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a person social relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'PER-SOC', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a person social relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'PER-SOC', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a person social relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'PHYS', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a physical relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'PHYS', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a physical relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'PHYS', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a physical relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'PHYS', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a physical relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'PHYS', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a physical relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'PHYS', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a physical relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('ORG', 'PHYS', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a physical relationship with organization entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'ART', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'ART', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'ART', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'ART', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'ART', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'ART', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'ART', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'GEN-AFF', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'GEN-AFF', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'GEN-AFF', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'GEN-AFF', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'GEN-AFF', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'GEN-AFF', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'GEN-AFF', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'ORG-AFF', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'ORG-AFF', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'ORG-AFF', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'ORG-AFF', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'ORG-AFF', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'ORG-AFF', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'ORG-AFF', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'PART-WHOLE', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'PART-WHOLE', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'PART-WHOLE', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'PART-WHOLE', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'PART-WHOLE', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'PART-WHOLE', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'PART-WHOLE', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'PER-SOC', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a person social relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'PER-SOC', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a person social relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'PER-SOC', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a person social relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'PER-SOC', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a person social relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'PER-SOC', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a person social relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'PER-SOC', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a person social relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'PER-SOC', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a person social relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'PHYS', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a physical relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'PHYS', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a physical relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'PHYS', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a physical relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'PHYS', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a physical relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'PHYS', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a physical relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'PHYS', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a physical relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('PER', 'PHYS', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a physical relationship with person entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'ART', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'ART', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'ART', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'ART', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'ART', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'ART', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'ART', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'GEN-AFF', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'GEN-AFF', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'GEN-AFF', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'GEN-AFF', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'GEN-AFF', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'GEN-AFF', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'GEN-AFF', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'ORG-AFF', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'ORG-AFF', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'ORG-AFF', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'ORG-AFF', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'ORG-AFF', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'ORG-AFF', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'ORG-AFF', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'PART-WHOLE', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'PART-WHOLE', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'PART-WHOLE', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'PART-WHOLE', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'PART-WHOLE', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'PART-WHOLE', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'PART-WHOLE', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'PER-SOC', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a person social relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'PER-SOC', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a person social relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'PER-SOC', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a person social relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'PER-SOC', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a person social relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'PER-SOC', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a person social relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'PER-SOC', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a person social relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'PER-SOC', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a person social relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'PHYS', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a physical relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'PHYS', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a physical relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'PHYS', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a physical relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'PHYS', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a physical relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'PHYS', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a physical relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'PHYS', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a physical relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('VEH', 'PHYS', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a physical relationship with vehicle entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'ART', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'ART', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'ART', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'ART', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'ART', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'ART', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'ART', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have an artifact relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'GEN-AFF', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'GEN-AFF', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'GEN-AFF', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'GEN-AFF', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'GEN-AFF', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'GEN-AFF', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'GEN-AFF', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a gen affilliation relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'ORG-AFF', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'ORG-AFF', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'ORG-AFF', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'ORG-AFF', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'ORG-AFF', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'ORG-AFF', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'ORG-AFF', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have an organization affiliation relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'PART-WHOLE', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'PART-WHOLE', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'PART-WHOLE', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'PART-WHOLE', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'PART-WHOLE', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'PART-WHOLE', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'PART-WHOLE', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a part whole relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'PER-SOC', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a person social relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'PER-SOC', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a person social relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'PER-SOC', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a person social relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'PER-SOC', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a person social relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'PER-SOC', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a person social relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'PER-SOC', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a person social relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'PER-SOC', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a person social relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'PHYS', 'FAC')": "find all facility entities in the context that have a physical relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'PHYS', 'GPE')": "find all geo political entities in the context that have a physical relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'PHYS', 'LOC')": "find all location entities in the context that have a physical relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'PHYS', 'ORG')": "find all organization entities in the context that have a physical relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'PHYS', 'PER')": "find all person entities in the context that have a physical relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'PHYS', 'VEH')": "find all vehicle entities in the context that have a physical relationship with weapon entity XXX.",
        "('WEA', 'PHYS', 'WEA')": "find all weapon entities in the context that have a physical relationship with weapon entity XXX."
    }
}